hubbell.com 2016-12-14

# Privacy Statement

Hubbell Incorporated and its divisions, subsidiaries, and affiliates are committed to protecting the privacy of our users. On certain websites, some type of information is collected about a user to make the website more useful for the user. This Website Visitor Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") describes how our information is collected from you and how we use it. **By visiting a Hubbell Incorporated website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.**

This Privacy Statement may change at any time and for any reason. We encourage you to look to this Privacy Statement each time you visit this website and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. You are also encouraged to review our Terms of Use.

The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our website.

Hubbell Incorporated may gather the following types of information:

  * **Information You Give Us**  
If you give personal information to us by entering it in a form or by some other mechanism, Hubbell Incorporated will use that information according to the policies expressed in this document. 
  * **Your IP Address**  
Hubbell Incorporated collects Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses for system administration and auditing website usage. Our servers log your IP address when a page is requested from our website. We may use this IP address to identify a specific user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of use of the website or to protect our services or customers. 
  * **Automatic Information**  
Like many websites, we use "cookies" or other types of clickstream data for websites that allow you to login to conduct business and access or provide non-public information. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Hubbell Incorporated products or services that require you to "sign in" and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, many Hubbell Incorporated websites do not require that you accept cookies. 

This website is not intentionally designed for or directed at children 13 years of age or younger without obtaining prior consent from a person with parental responsibility. It is our practice never to knowingly collect or maintain information about anyone 13 years of age or younger (such as a child's name or e-mail address). Please contact Hubbell Incorporated Legal Department at (475) 882-4231 if you think we may have inadvertently collected such information.

Use of the information:

There are no restrictions to the way Hubbell Incorporated can use or share anonymous information. We will use anonymous information to help us make our websites more useful to visitors and for other business purposes. We may prepare reports and other materials using anonymous information. Since these reports and materials contain no personal information, we may share them with others.

All information that is not personal to you or someone else, such as questions, comments, ideas and suggestions that we refer to as “Feedback” shall be considered as non-confidential information. Hubbell Incorporated will be free to disclose and use the information for any purpose and through any means without any obligation whatsoever to any user, e.g., Hubbell Incorporated is free to reproduce, use, disclose, exhibit, display, transform, commercialize, create derivative works and distribute the Feedback to others without limitation. By choosing to send a message to Hubbell Incorporated, you acknowledge that all feedback will be considered to be non-confidential. Further, Hubbell Incorporated shall be free to use any ideas, inventions, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such Feedback for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products incorporating such Feedback.

Some of Hubbell Incorporated’s websites provide additional information and capabilities to users who register with the website to receive a username and password. That registration process will require that you provide Personal Information.

Hubbell Incorporated may use the Personal Information we collect to:

  * respond to your requests
  * contact you, via e-mail, regular mail, telephone or otherwise
  * to develop records, including records of your personal information
  * to develop and improve programs, products, services and content
  * to enforce Terms of Use and Privacy Statement and other rules about your use of this website
  * to protect Hubbell Incorporated’s rights or property
  * to comply with a law or regulation, court order or other legal process
  * respond to your requests

By submitting personal information (such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc.), you agree that we may keep a record of it and may use it in accordance with the above. We also may use your personal information to help us in our business, including but not limited to improving our website, marketing and/or product development. Any information received by a Hubbell Incorporated website will be stored securely by using methods and protections that are as reasonably secure as practical, and only used by Hubbell Incorporated and its authorized affiliates (sales reps, etc.). Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we do not sell such information to others.

The Hubbell Incorporated computers (called “servers”) process and store an enormous amount of information every day. These computer records are called “log files”. Log files are used for analysis, research, auditing, and other purposes, as described above. After this information has been used, it is stored in a location that is inaccessible from the internet and is available to only a limited number of persons within Hubbell Incorporated. Until the information is stored, your Hubbell Incorporated ID may remain in our active server log files. E-mail addresses provided at registration or by other mechanism may be used by Hubbell Incorporated or its affiliates for communication with you about an order or its status and, unless you opt-out, for communications about updates, products, and service information.

Except as otherwise written in this Privacy Statement, we will keep your personal information private and will not share it with others, unless the disclosure is necessary to: 

  * comply with a law or regulation, court order, subpoena or other legal process
  * protect our rights or property
  * enforce our Terms of Use or this Privacy Statement
  * protect someone’s health or safety

EU and Swiss Residents:

Hubbell Incorporated recognizes that the European Union and Switzerland have implemented “omnibus” data protection regimes established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC) and the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection, respectively. Among other things, these laws require “adequate protection” for the transfer of certain individually identifiable data about individuals in European Union member countries and Switzerland to Hubbell Incorporated operations in the United States. Hubbell Incorporated complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Hubbell Incorporated has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Hubbell Incorporated provides its employees in Europe and Switzerland with information regarding the data transfers that are covered by Safe Harbor via separate policies and procedures. Any employee in Europe or Switzerland that cannot resolve his or her issue directly with Hubbell Incorporated is permitted to contact his or her local data protection authority for further assistance and information. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Hubbell Incorporated’s certification, please visit: http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/
